1800hotels.com 2012-08-18

# Privacy & Security - 1 800 Hotels

**1800Hotels.com Privacy Policy**

Your Privacy Rights

We want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. We want to provide you with the means to control your privacy and give you a way to voice questions or concerns you may have.

Information is collected from you to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. By knowing customer preferences, services and special offerings can be tailored to provide superior levels of convenience. Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked at various times to provide information such as your name, email address or information about what you like and do not like. On other occasions when we provide items for purchase online, we may request your credit card number to conclude the transaction or your mailing address to insure proper delivery. Consistent with the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from minors.

 **What Information Do We Collect?**

We collect information in several different ways. We collect:

The domain name of visitors to our Web pages, The e-mail addresses of those visitors who volunteer them, User-specific information on the pages visitors access, and information such as survey information, Postal address, telephone numbers and site registrations that you provide voluntarily. Like many other commercial websites, our websites may employ a standard technology called a “cookie” to collect information about how our site is used.

 **Who Is Collecting the Information?**

The information that you provide is collected by 1800Hotels.com.

 **How the Information Is Used?**

We use the information that we collect to understand your preferences and history. With this information we can tailor our services and special offerings to provide superior levels of convenience and service on a one-to-one basis. We also use the collected information to improve the design of our Web pages.

We will not transfer information to competitors. Information about your preferences is only used to help us understand the products and services that might be attractive to you. If you provide us with your e-mail address, we may occasionally send you e-mail offers, informing you about products and services. If you provide us with your postal address, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. These offers may be based on information you provided us in your responses to our surveys and on your history with us as a customer.

 **Information Distribution**

Although unlikely, we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information to the appropriate governmental authorities. If requested as part of a legal proceeding, we will provide this information upon receipt of the appropriate documentation.

Other companies which could place advertising on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising or content through the use of cookies. Due to the way the Internet technically operates, we cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers or content providers if you have any questions about their use of the information they collect.

There may be links that will let you leave our site. We do not control the links or their sites and we are not responsible for the contents of any linked site or any link contained in a linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement of the site. The use and/or privacy provided by the operator of a linked site as to any information you provide in accessing a linked site is in no way subject to our privacy policy. Each linked site may have its own policy that could differ considerably from our policy, or the linked site may not display any privacy policy at all. In any case, even though a linked site is accessed through our site, we cannot be responsible for any use that a linked site may make of your information.

 **Declining Offers**

If you do not want to receive posted or e-mail offers from us or from our partners, please let us know by sending us an e-mail message to [info@1800hotels.com](mailto:info@1800hotels.com) telling us that you do not want to receive offers. Our e-mailed offers also include instructions for unsubscribing. If you want to be removed from our postal mailing list, please provide us with your complete name, agency name and address.

 **What Kind of Security Procedures Are in Place to Protect the Loss, Misuse or Alteration of Information Under the Company’s Control?**

We operate secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall, malware filtering and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers. Any particularly sensitive information, such as a customer’s credit card number, is encrypted prior to transmission.

 **How You Can Correct Any Inaccuracies in the Information**

To update the information retained about you, or to deactivate your account, please email us at [info@1800hotels.com](mailto:info@1800hotels.com)

 **Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using this site, you agree to our Privacy Policy. We may also update the Policy from time to time, so please be sure to visit this site often to see if anything has changed. If we post changes and you continue to use the site, you will be deemed to have agreed to the changes.

 **Company Contact**

Contact us via email at [info@1800hotels.com](mailto:info@1800hotels.com).
